Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Health and Hospital Corporation, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 1989, Folder 18-32)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Health Research Council, 1960-1963, 1973 (Offsite-box 1989, Folder 33-34)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Health Services Administration, 1967-1979 (Offsite-box 1989, Folder 35)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Higher Education, Board of, 1976-1980 (Offsite-box 1989, Folder 36)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Higher Education, Board of, 1957-1970 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 1-4)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Highway, Department of, 1963-1982 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 5)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Hospitals, Department of, 1957-1969 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 6-7)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Housing and Development Administration, 1966-1986 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 8-9)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Housing and Redevelopment Board, 1960-1967, 1989 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 10-12)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Housing Authority, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 13-19)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Housing Development Corporation, 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 20)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Housing Preservation and Development, Department of, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 21-24)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Human Resources Administration, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 1990, Folder 25-31)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Human Resources Administration, 1965-1982 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 1-8)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Human Rights, Commission on, 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 9-12)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: I, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 13-14)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Industrial Development Agency, New York City, 1977-1987 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 15)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Industrial Development Corporation, New York City, 1963-1966 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 16)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Inquiry into Energy Failures, Commission of, 1977 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 17)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Intergroup Relations, Commission on, 1957 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 18)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Intergroup Relations, Committee on, 1978 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 19)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Investigation, Department of, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 20-21)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: J, 1958-1992 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 22)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: K, 1982 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 23)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Knapp Commission (Police), 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 24-25)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: L, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 26)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Labor, Department of, 1955-1966, 1981 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 27)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Labor Relations, Office of, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 28)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Landmark Preservation Commission, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 29-31)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Landmark Preservation Commission, 1961-1980 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 1-2)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Law, Department of, 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 8)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Legislative Office of Budget Review, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 9)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Licenses, Department of, 1955-1966 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 10)
  - New York State: Government: Departments and Agencies: Liquor Authority, State, 1963 (Offsite-box 2077, Folder 21)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Maa-Mz, 1957-1992, undated (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 11-20)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Management and Budget, Office of, 1961-1983 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 21-23)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Manhattan Borough Board, 1977 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 24)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Manpower and Career Development Agency, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 25)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Marine and Aviation, Department of, 1952-1980, 1990 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 26)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Markets, Department of, 1960-1967 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 27)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Advisory Panel on Decentralization of the New York City Schools, 1967, undated (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 28)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Coalition on Long-Term Financing, 1978 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 29)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Commission on State-City Relations, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 30)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Committee on Slum Clearance, 1959 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 1)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Committee on Bigotry, 1968 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 2)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Committee on the Judiciary, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 3)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Council Against Poverty, 1966 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 4)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Council on the Environment, 1972-1986 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 5)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Criminal Justice Coordinating Council, 1969-1982 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 6)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Emergency Control Board, 1978 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 7)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Management Advisory Board, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 8)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Narcotics Control Council, 1971 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 9)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Office for Volunteers, 1968 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 10)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Rent Guidelines Board, 1969 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 11)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Subway Service Watchdog Commission, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 12)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Task Force on Air Pollution, 1966 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 13)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Urban Action Task Force, 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 14)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Midtown Planning and Development, Office of, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 15)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mollen Commission, 1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 16)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Municipal Services Administration, 1977 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 17)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: N, 1952, 1966, 1982-1983, 1992 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 18)
  - New York State: Government: Departments and Agencies: Narcotic Addiction Control Commission, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 2077, Folder 22-23)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Neighborhood City Halls Program, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 19)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Neighborhood Government, Office of, 1972 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 20)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Neighborhood Services, Office of, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 21)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: O, 1975-1988 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 22)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Off-Track Betting Corporation, 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 23-26)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Organization, 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 27-29)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: P, 1939, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 30)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Parking Violations Bureau, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 31-34)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Parks, Department of, 1963-1970, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 35-41)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Parks, Department of, 1955-1962 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 1)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Parks, Recreation and Cultural Affairs Administration, 1982 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 2)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Parks and Recreations, Department of, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 3)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Planning, Department of City, 1980-1990 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 4)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Planning Commission, City, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 5-17)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Port Development and Promotion, New York City Council on, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 18)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Ports, International Trade and Commerce, Department of, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 19)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Poverty, Council Against, 1965-1979 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 20)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Probation, Department of, 1956, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 21)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Proposed, 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 22-25)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Proposed, 1966 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 3)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Public Events, Department of, 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 26)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Public Works, Department of, 1961-1963, 1978, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 27)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Publications, 1962, 1977-1986 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 28)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Purchase, Department of, 1965-1967, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 29)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: R, 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 30)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Rankin Committee (Police), 1970 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 31)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Real Estate, Bureau of, 1959-1978 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 32)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Real Estate, Bureau of, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 4)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Real Estate, Department of, 1959-1978 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 33)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Recreation and Cultural Affairs Administration, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 34)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Rent and Housing Maintenance, Department of, 1977 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 35)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Rent and Housing Maintenance, Office of, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 36)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Rent and Rehabilitation Administration, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 1)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Rent Guidelines Board, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 2)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Sa-Sz, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 3-7)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Sanitation, Department of, 1939-1993, undated (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 5-21)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Service Coordination, Office of, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 22)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Service Corporation, National, 1984 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 23)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Site Selection Board, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 24)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Social Services, Department of, 1967-1990 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 25-27)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Stabilization Reserve Corporation, 1974 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 28)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Standards and Appeals, Board of, 1959-1989 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 29)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Staten Island Rapid Transit Operating Authority, 1972-1985 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 30)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Taa-Tz, 1957-1992 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 31-33)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Tax Commission, 1965-1986 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 34)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Taxi and Limousine Commission, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 35-38)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Temporary Commission on City Finances, 1965-1981 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 39)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Temporary Commission on Education, 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 1993, Folder 1)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Traffic, Department of, 1956-1990, undated (Offsite-box 1993, Folder 2-4)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Traffic Operations, Bureau of, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 1993, Folder 5)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Transit Authority, 1961-1966, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 1993, Folder 6-26)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Transit Authority, 1955-1964 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 1-2)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Transit Construction Fund, 1972 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 3)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Transportation Administration, 1966, 1977-1978, 1990 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 4)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Transportation Council, 1966 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 5)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Transportation, Department of, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 6-8)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 9-15)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: U, 1956-1992 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 16)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: United Nations, New York City Commission to the, 1963-1988 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 17)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: United Nations and for the Consular Corps, New York City Commission for the, 1973-1991 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 18)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: University Relations, Office of, 1968 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 19)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: V, 1970-1991 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 20)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Volunteer Corps, City, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 21)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: W, 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 22)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Water Resources, Department of, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 23)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Water Supply, Board of, 1954-1979 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 24)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Water Supply, Bureau of, 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 25)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Water Supply, Gas and Electricity, Department of, 1959-1968 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 26-28)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Weights and Measures, Bureau, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 29)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Welfare, Department of, 1954-1977 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 30-33)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Y, 1959-1961, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 8)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Youth Board, 1952-1982 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 9-12)
  - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Youth Services Agency, 1969-1972, 1992 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 13)
  - New York City: Government: Deputy Mayor, 1949-1992 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 14-17)
  - New York City: Government: District Attorney, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 18-20)
  - New York City: Government: Equipment, 1983, 1989 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 21)
  - New York City: Government: Investigations, 1932, 1959-1961, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 22-24)
  - New York City: Government: Mayor, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 25-32)
  - New York City: Government: Mayor, 1932-1969 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 1-3)
  - New York City: Government: Mayor: Residences, 1961-1967, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 4)
  - New York City: History, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 5-19)
  - New York City: History: Associations, 1970-1989 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 20)
  - New York City: History: Associations: Brooklyn Historical Society, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 21)
  - New York City: History: Associations: New-York Historical Society, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 22)
  - New York City: History: Associations: New-York Historical Society, 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 1-2)
  - New York City: History: Diamond Jubilee, 1973 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 3)
  - New York City: History: Golden Jubilee, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 4)
  - New York City: Islands, 1956-1988 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 5)
  - New York City: Islands: B-R, 1932, 1949-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 6-16)
  - New York City: Islands: Roosevelt Island, Franklin D., 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 17-20)
  - New York City: Islands: S-W, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 21-23)
  - New York City: Laws, 1966-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 24)
  - New York City: Manhattan, 1940-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 25-27)
  - New York City: Memorials and Monuments, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 28-32)
  - New York City: Metropolitan Area, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 34)
  - New York City: Metropolitan Area, 1956-1987 (Offsite-box 1995, Folder 1-10)
  - New York City: Metropolitan Area: Transit, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1995, Folder 11-20)
  - New York City: Metropolitan Area: Transit, 1956-1961 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 1-3)
  - New York City: Metropolitan Area: Tri-State Regional Planning Commission, 1971-1982 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 4)
  - New York City: Name, 1959, 1976-1988 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 5)
  - New York City: Natural Resources, 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 6)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods, 1949-1993 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 7-17)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: A-B, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 18-19)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Battery, 1957-1988 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 20)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Battery Park City, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 21-23)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Battery Park City, 1968-1979 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 1-2)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bay Ridge, 1973-1987 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 3)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bayside, 1959, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 4)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 5-11)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bellevue South, 1965 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 12)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bensonhurst, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 13)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Borough Park, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 14)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bowery, 1942-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 15-17)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Broadway, 1939-1984, undated (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 18)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Brooklyn Heights, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 19)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Brownsville, 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 20)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bushwick, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 21)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: C, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 22-23)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Canarsie, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 1)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Chelsea, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 2)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Chinatown, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 3-8)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Civic Center Manhattan, 1960-1966, 1989 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 9)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Clinton, 1952-1959, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 10)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Cobble Hill, 1977-1990 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 11)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Columbus Circle, 1955-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 12)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Coney Island, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 13)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Cooper Square, 1956-1991 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 14)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Corona, 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 15)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Crown Heights, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 16-18)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Crown Heights, 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 1)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: D, 1971-1992 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 2)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Downtown and Lower Manhattan, 1955-1991 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 3-8)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: E, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 9)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: East New York, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 10)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: East Side, 1932-1993 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 11-15)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: East Village, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 16-18)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: F, 1971-1991 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 19)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Flatbush, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 1)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Flushing, 1946-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 2)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Foley Square, 1965-1985 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 3)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Forest Hills, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 4)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Forest Hills Gardens, 1976-1989 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 5)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Fort Greene, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 6)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: G, 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 7)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Garment District, 1949, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 8)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Gramercy Park, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 9)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Grand Central, 1957-1991 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 10)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Grand Concourse, 1967-1988 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 11)
  - New York City: Neighborhoods: Greenpoint, 1949, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 12)